Guide to the Carling I. Malouf Papers 1891-2006
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Subject Files, 1891-2006; Series II; 30.75 linear feet
  - Montana Archaeology, volume IV, 1956-1994; Publications, clippings, student field notes, photographs with captions, correspondence, notes and maps (Box-folder 37/4-5)
  - Montana Historic Sites, St. Mary's Mission, undated (Box-folder 71/13)
  - Montana History, Photographs, 1952-1967 (Box-folder 71/14 (1 of 2))
  - Montana History, Photographs, 1952-1967 (Box-folder 72/1 (2 of 2))
  - Montana House Bill 343, 1973 (Box-folder 72/2)
  - Montana Indians, Federal Bills, 1954-1956 (Box-folder 72/3)
  - Montana Landless Indians, 1957-1980; Notes on Hill 57, publications, meeting minutes from the Citizen’s Committee on Great Falls Indian Affairs, study prepared for Committee on Great Falls Indian Affairs (Box-folder 37/6-9)
  - Montana Native Americans Clippings, 2001 and undated (Box-folder 38/1-2)
  - Montana Native Americans, circa 1958-2000; Clippings and publications (Box-folder 38/3-6)
  - Montana Petroglyphs and Pictographs, circa 1950-1992 (Box-folder 39/1-4)
  - Montana Prehistoric and Historic Archaeological Sites, Helena Area, undated (Box-folder 72/4)
  - Montana, Flathead, undated (Box-folder 72/5)
  - Montana, The Magazine of Western History, Correspondence, 1999 (Box-folder 72/6)
  - William Mulloy, Pictograph Cave and Easter Island Works, 1941-2003 (Box-folder 53/7-8)
  - William Mulloy, Photograph, 1937 (Box-folder 72/7)
  - Museum of the Plans Indian, Browning, Montana, 1954-1964 (Box-folder 39/5-7)
  - Museums, including Fort Missoula, 1957-1987 (Box-folder 40/1-3)
  - National Congress of American Indians, 1955-1962 (Box-folder 40/4-6)
  - National Science Foundation, Application for Aboriginal - White Site in Western Montana, 1969 (Box-folder 72/8)
  - Native American Alcohol Problems, circa 1969-1980 (Box-folder 41/1-4)
  - Native American Colleges, circa 1975-2002; Salish Kootenai College and other college listings (Box-folder 41/5)
  - Native American Education, volume I, circa 1958-2000; Clippings, conference reports, newsletters, publications, student papers, University reports (Box-folder 41/6-8)
  - Native American Education, volume II, circa 1971-2001; Clippings, conference reports, newsletters, publications, student papers, University reports (Box-folder 42/1-3)
  - Native American Legal and Cases, Laws, etc., 1953-1984 (Box-folder 72/9-11 (1-3 of 4))
  - Native American Legal and Cases, Laws, etc., 1953-1984 (Box-folder 73/1 (4 of 4))
  - Native American Personal Histories, 1963-1984 and undated (Box-folder 73/2)
  - Native American Personalities A-Z, circa 1951-2001; Clippings, correspondence, publications, study reports, transcripts from interview with Yellowtail, court proceedings transcript (Box-folder 42/4)
  - Native Americans in Sports, 2001 and n.d. (Box-folder 42/5)
  - Native Americans: Latin America History and Pre-History, 1999 (Box-folder 42/6)
  - Native Americans, Unidentified in Columbia River Basin, Postcards and Photographs, 1928-1965 and undated (Box-folder 73/3)
  - Native Americans with some Anthropology Connections, 1933-2004 (Box-folder 64/5)
  - Ninemile Canyon, Utah, undated (Box-folder 73/4)
  - Louis Ninepipes, 1954-1974 (Box-folder 73/5)
  - Northern Montana College Indian Conferences, circa 1969-1975 (Box-folder 42/7-10)
  - Northwest Anthropological Conference, 1951-1969 (Box-folder 73/6-7)
  - Notebook, undated (Box-folder 73/8)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 43/1)
  - Omer Stewart, 1932-1984; Publications and correspondence (Box-folder 43/2-5)
  - Paleontologic Trends in Evolution, undated (Box-folder 73/9)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1989 (Box-folder 73/10)
  - Photos: Montana Archaeological Specimens, circa 1930-circa 1955 (Box-folder 43/6-8)
  - Photos: Montana Archaeological Specimens, circa 1950-circa 1955 (Box-folder 44/1)
  - Photos: Montana Archaeological Specimens also Sites, 1950-1966 (Box-folder 44/2-5)
  - Photos: Thain White Collection, 1889-1970; Blackfeet, Salish, Kutenai (Kootenai) (Box-folder 44/6-7)
  - Photos: Thain White Collection, 1889-1970; Blackfeet, Salish, Kutenai (Kootenai) (Box-folder 45/1)
  - Plains Anthropology, 1948-1963 (Box-folder 45/2-4)
  - Plains Indians, 1952-1984; Clippings, publications, newsletters from historical societies, photographs, notes (Box-folder 45/5-8)
  - Plat of Area Being Studied as Possible Site of David Thompson's Saleesh House, 1961 (Box-folder OS 77/2)
  - Public Gambling on Reservations, n.d. (Box-folder 46/1)
  - Publication on Indians (photocopy), 1890 (Box-folder 46/2)
  - Publications, 1938-2003 (Box-folder 74/1-6 (1-6 of 14))
  - Publications, 1938-2003 (Box-folder 75/1-8 (7-14 of 14))
  - Race and Minorities, volume I, circa 1964-1999; Clippings, publications, Akwesasne Notes newspapers (Box-folder 46/3-5)
  - Race and Minorities, volume II, circa 1968-2001; Clippings, publications, Akwesasne Notes newspapers (Box-folder 46/6)
  - Race and Minorities, volume II, circa 1968-2001; Clippings, publications, Akwesasne Notes newspapers (Box-folder 47/1-2)
  - Race and Minorities, volume III, 1939-2001; Clippings, publications, Akwesasne Notes newspapers (Box-folder 47/3)
  - Ralph Linton, 1916-1950; Correspondence and publications (Box-folder 47/4)
  - Rebecca Timmons Thesis: Historic Archaeology, 1959-1976 (Box-folder 47/5-7)
  - Regis College and other Indian Institutes, circa 1968 and n.d.; Correspondence, student papers, reports, and publications (Box-folder 47/8-9 (1-2 of 4))
  - Regis College and other Indian Institutes, circa 1968 and n.d.; Correspondence, student papers, reports, and publications (Box-folder 48/1-2 (3-4 of 4))
  - Restricted Sales, 1949-1957 (Box-folder 76/1)
  - Robert Wood, Doctoral Dissertation, 1968 (Box-folder 48/3-4)
  - Rocky Boy Reservation, 1954-1993; Cree and Chippewa (Box-folder 48/5-8)
  - Roy Austin, 1939-1997; Notes and correspondence (Box-folder 48/9-10 (1-2 of 4))
  - Roy Austin, 1939-1997; Notes and correspondence (Box-folder 49/1-2 (3-4 of 4))
  - Salish and Pend d'Orielle Ceremonies and Dance, undated (Box-folder 76/2)
  - Salish House, 1973 (Box-folder 76/2)
  - Salvage Archaeology, 1981 (Box-folder 76/3)
  - Shamanism, 1970 and undated (Box-folder 76/7)
  - Sharing Ideas, Division of Indian Education, State Department of Public Instruction, Phoenix, Arizona, 1965 (Box-folder 76/5)
  - Shumate Papers, circa 1959-1963 (Box-folder 49/3-4)
  - Sister Providentia, circa 1969-1974 (Box-folder 49/5)
  - Society for American Archaeology, Correspondence, 1959-1997 (Box-folder 76/6)
  - Stevensville Historical Society, Correspondence, 1970 (Box-folder 76/8)
  - Thain White Photographs, Flathead Lake Area, circa 1890 (Box-folder 49/6-8 (1-3 of 4))
  - Thain White Photographs, Flathead Lake Area, circa 1890 (Box-folder 50/1 (4 of 4))
  - Thain White Photographs, Flathead Lake Area, circa 1900-1955 (Box-folder 50/2-3)
  - "The American Indian," by Duncan Strong, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 76/9-10)
  - "The Bison Drive of the Blackfeet Indians," by Claude E. Schaffer, 1965 (Box-folder 76/11)
  - "The Impact of Modern Highways on American Indian Country," by Robert J. Trier and Vern S. Kubit, 1965 (Box-folder 76/12)
  - Thunderbird Newsletters, circa 1977-1985 (Box-folder 50/4)
  - Trading Post at St. Ignatius, Montana, Correspondence, 1985 (Box-folder 76/14)
  - Trail of Broken Treaties, A.I.M., Wounded Knee, Trials, volume I, circa 1972-1975 (Box-folder 50/5-6)
  - Trail of Broken Treaties, A.I.M., Wounded Knee, Trials, volume II, circa 1973-1974 (Box-folder 51/1-2)
  - Trail of Broken Treaties, A.I.M., Wounded Knee, Trials, volume III, circa 1971-1993 (Box-folder 51/3-4)
  - Trail of Broken Treaties, A.I.M., Wounded Knee, Trials, volume IV, circa 1973-1974 (Box-folder 51/5-6)
  - Trail of Broken Treaties, A.I.M., Wounded Knee, Trials, volume V, circa 1972-1974 (Box-folder 52/1-2)
  - Tribal Termination, circa 1954-1999 (Box-folder 52/3-5)
  - Tribes of Western Montana, Map, undated (Box-folder 76/15)
  - United States Land Commission Cases, circa 1951-1961 (Box-folder 53/4-6)
  - Urban Indians, 1967 and n.d. (Box-folder 52/6-7)
  - Utah Archaeology, undated (Box-folder 76/16)
  - Vanderburg Camp, 1990 (Box-folder 76/17)
  - Western Montana College, circa 1975-1977 (Box-folder 53/1)
  - Western Montana Indian Clippings, circa 1912-1978 (Box-folder 53/2-3)
  - Thain White, Retyped Letter, 1995 (Box-folder 76/18)
  - Willow Creek, Little Bear Creek, and Marshall Creek Sites, 1995 (Box-folder 76/19)
  - Women who are changing Indian Country, circa 2001 (Box-folder 53/9)
  - Workshop on American Indian Affairs, 1964 (Box-folder 76/20)
- Audio Materials, circa 1920-1978; Series III; 1.5 linear feet
  Contains reel-to-reel audio and audiocassettes. A portion of this series is recorded talks and lectures of Carling Malouf, and recordings of the songs and stories of Native American tribes of the Northwest. Another portion consists of copies of prerecorded materials related to the Native Americans in the southwest.
  Most of the audio in this series of Native American music, stories, and interviews are restricted. See archivist for details.
  - 4th Annual Indian Institute, Dusenberry session, undated; Audio quality very poor. (Box-item 54/1)
  - Carling Malouf talking about Mulloy, audio cassette, April 16, 1978; Digitized copy available. (Box-item 54/2)
  - Interview with Zosel Sisters, Grant Kohrs National Ranch, audio cassette, September 6, 1973 (Box-item 54/3)
  - Flathead Indian Songs, recorded by Alan Merriam, audio cassette, undated; Original audio held at the Library of Congress. (Box-item 54/4)
  - New Guinea, Chimbu, singing across valley, Mt Hagen Church, women singing, audio cassette, undated; Original audio held at Indiana University Archives of Traditional Music. (Box-item 54/5)
  - Blackfeet, Browning Inc. bar, reel-to-reel audio, undated; Interviews about educational and employment opportunities on Montana reservations. (Box-item 54/6)
  - Sister Providencia and others speaking on a panel discussion about landless Indians in Great Falls, reel-to-reel audio, undated (Box-item 54/7)
  - Indian conference on discrimination, Northwest-affiliated tribes, reel-to-reel audio, undated; Audio quality very poor. (Box-item 54/8)
  - Carling Malouf speaking at a conference in Great Falls on Indian education, reel-to-reel audio, 1967; Digitized copy available. (Box-item 54/9)
  - Bob Howard talking about employment and educational opportunities on the Blackfeet Reservation, reel-to-reel audio, undated (Box-item 54/10)
  - Headstart, children reciting days of the week, reel-to-reel audio, undated (Box-item 54/11)
  - Public talk at Institute of Indian Affairs: Robert Yellowtail (Crow); Edward Dosy Whiteman (Crow), Walter McDonald (Flathead), reel-to-reel audio, undated; Digitized copy available. (Box-item 55/12)
  - Robert Yellowtail, Paradise Dams, reel-to-reel audio, undated; This audio may be a continuation of the audio on reel #16. Digitized copy available. (Box-item 55/13)
  - Institute 1 and 2 side; Kids side 1; Raymond Gray, Hill 57, reel-to-reel audio, December 11, 1957 (Box-item 55/14)
  - Montana Inter-tribal Policy Board: Side 1, heirship bill and judicare; Side 2, heirship and taxation, reel-to-reel audio, December 2, 1966 - December 3, 1966 (Box-item 55/15)
  - Alcoholism, Side II: comments after tribal council dinner (includes all of Bill Carmichael's speech), reel-to-reel audio, January 12, 1968 (Box-item 55/16)
  - Montana Committee on Human Relations meeting: Tascher, Hansen, DeMers, Melis, Gunderson, and Galloway, reel-to-reel audio, undated (Box-item 55/17)
  - Grant Creek rock piles, Cory Clark, reel-to-reel audio, undated; Audio quality very poor. (Box-item 55/18)
  - 1st session, Northwest tribes, January 11: Robert Pantzer, Carling Malouf, Pope, and Hall, reel-to-reel audio, circa 1960s (Box-item 55/19)
  - 2nd day, Leonard Kenilsworth and Father Kohlman, reel-to-reel audio, undated; Audio quality very poor. (Box-item 55/20)
  - Good Friday church service in St. Ignatius about religious beliefs among Flathead, Salish, Kootenai, and Blackfeet, reel-to-reel audio, undated (Box-item 55/21)
  - Schultz, Blackfeet songs, reel-to-reel audio, circa 1920s; Original audio held at Indiana University Folklore Institute, accession #64102640. (Box-item 55/22)
  - Schultz, Blackfeet songs, reel-to-reel audio, circa 1920s; Original audio held at Indiana University Folklore Institute, accession #64102640. (Box-item 55/23)
  - Chimbu, New Guinea, John Ross #1, reel-to-reel audio, 1963; Original audio held at Indiana University Archives of Traditional Music. (Box-item 55/24)
  - Chimbu, New Guinea, John Ross #2, reel-to-reel audio, 1963; Original audio held at Indiana University Archives of Traditional Music. (Box-item 55/25)
  - Southwest Indians, Fred Harvey record, RESTRICTED, audio cassette, circa 1930s (Box-item 56/26)
  - Aztec, Arlee, Montana, RESTRICTED, audio cassette, undated (Box-item 56/27)
  - Carling Malouf interview with John Woodenlegs, RESTRICTED, audio cassette, undated (Box-item 56/28)
  - John Woodenlegs and Carling Malouf, RESTRICTED, audio cassette, undated; Likely a continuation of audio #29. (Box-item 56/29)
  - Dr. Joe A. Campbell and Johnny Arlee, RESTRICTED, audio cassette, undated (Box-item 56/30)
  - Comanche Peyote songs, RESTRICTED, audio cassette, undated (Box-item 56/31)
  - Flathead Indian chant sung in St. Mary's Mission before 1890, Bitterroot Valley, RESTRICTED, audio cassette, 1951; Singers include Ellen Bigsam, Paul Charlot, Joe Bigsam, and Father Cornelius Byrnes. (Box-item 56/32)
  - Original Peyote songs, Philip Bear Shoe (alias Kenneth Parker), RESTRICTED, audio cassette, undated (Box-item 56/33)
  - Flathead Interviews: Bert Hansen, Carling Malouf, Eneas Granjo, RESTRICTED, audio cassette, undated; Audio of someone telling Native American stories. (Box-item 56/34)
  - Montana Archaeology Society, RESTRICTED, reel-to-reel audio, undated; Audio of someone telling Native American stories. (Box-item 56/35)
  - Anthropology, Bob Adams, tape 2, RESTRICTED, reel-to-reel audio, undated (Box-item 56/36)
  - Story by Baptiste Lefthand, RESTRICTED, reel-to-reel audio, undated (Box-item 56/37)
  - Rocky Boy, music, RESTRICTED, reel-to-reel audio, undated (Box-item 56/38)
  - Interview about Salish language and culture, RESTRICTED, reel-to-reel audio, undated; Audio quality very poor. (Box-item 56/39)
  - Kootenai Monument Dedication, RESTRICTED, reel-to-reel audio, November 4, 1972 (Box-item 56/40)
  - John Adams, Bob Adams, J. Oneil, RESTRICTED, reel-to-reel audio, undated (Box-item 56/41)
  - Father Cornelius Byrnes and Henry Matt, RESTRICTED, reel-to-reel audio, undated; Audio quality very poor. (Box-item 57/42)
  - Thain White and Carling Malouf interview Lasso Stasso, RESTRICTED, reel-to-reel audio, undated (Box-item 57/43)
  - Indian Dances: mostly Blackfoot (some Merriam), Flatheads, students work, RESTRICTED, reel-to-reel audio, Spring 1955 (Box-item 57/44)
  - Charles Hall: 14 songs and stories, RESTRICTED, reel-to-reel audio, July 31, 1969 - August 1, 1969 (Box-item 57/45)
  - Blue Jay Dance, Felix Bruce, RESTRICTED, reel-to-reel audio, undated (Box-item 57/46)
  - Pend d'Oreille tales and music, RESTRICTED, reel-to-reel audio, March 1960 (Box-item 57/47)
  - Charles Hall, 8 songs, RESTRICTED, reel-to-reel audio, August 2, 1969 (Box-item 57/48)
  - Flathead Songs, Lasso Stasso, Baptist Mathias, RESTRICTED, reel-to-reel audio, undated (Box-item 57/49)
  - Kenneth Parker, Comanche, grandson of Quanah Parker, Peyote songs, RESTRICTED, reel-to-reel audio, undated (Box-item 57/50)
  - Blackfeet songs, RESTRICTED, reel-to-reel audio, undated (Box-item 57/51)
  - Charles Hall, Sr., 15 Songs, RESTRICTED, reel-to-reel audio, July 31, 1969 (Box-item 57/52)
  - Charles Hall, 14 songs, Nakoda Assiniboine, RESTRICTED, reel-to-reel audio, August 1, 1969 (Box-item 57/53)
  - Bigsam (possibly Mose Bigsam) describes the Blue Jay dance ceremony, RESTRICTED, reel-to-reel audio, undated (Box-item 57/54)
  - Someone telling Native American stories, RESTRICTED, reel-to-reel audio, undated; This might be a duplicate of other audio in the collection. (Box-item 57/55)
- Slides, 1939-1975; Series IV; 5.0 linear feet
  This series contains slides. Boxes 60 and 61 of this collection, including the slide index, are reproductions of slides in other boxes of the collection. These reproductions were created by Anthropology Professor G. G. Weix in 2004 from original slides held by Carling Malouf. Weix donated these slides to the Archives prior to the acquistion of the original Malouf Slides. The reminder of the slides were donated to the Archives by the Malouf family. Some of these images were taken by Carling Malouf, others are commercial images likely used by him in the classroom. In 2012 slides originally received in slide carousels were transferred to clear sleeves to enhance preservation and access.
  - Index for slides, created by G. G. Weix, 1939-1975 (Box-folder 60/1)
  - Along the Old Spanish Trail, 1946 and undated (Box-folder 60/2)
  - Blackfeet, undated (Box-folder 60/3)
  - Blackfoot River, 1969 (Box-folder 60/4)
  - Flathead and Pend d'Orielle, 1941-1973 and undated (Box-folder 60/5-6)
  - Fort Owen, 1957-1975 and undated (Box-folder 60/7)
  - Goshute, 1939-1970 and undated (Box-folder 60/8)
  - Kutenai (Kootenai), 1952-1972 and undated (Box-folder 61/1)
  - Plains Indians Arts and Crafts, undated (Box-folder 61/2)
  - Plains Tribes, undated (Box-folder 61/3)
  - Saleesh House, 1959-1973 and; undated (Box-folder 61/4)
  - Skeletal / Burial, circa 1970 (Box-folder 78/1)
  - Indians, Flathead and Pend D'Orielle, Tray 2, undated (Box-folder 79/1)
  - Fort Missoula, undated (Box-folder 79/2)
  - Saleesh House, undated (Box-folder 79/3)
  - Prehistory, Columbia River Western Montana, undated (Box-folder 79/4)
  - Missouri River, Headwaters, undated (Box-folder 79/5)
  - Indians, Gosiute, Tray 1, undated (Box-folder 79/6)
  - Indians, Flathead and Pend D'Orielle, Tray 1, undated (Box-folder 79/7)
  - Blackfeet, undated (Box-folder 79/8)
  - Indians, Gosiute, Tray 2, undated (Box-folder 79/9)
  - Montana Archaeology, Artifacts, undated (Box-folder 79/10)
  - Blackfoot River, Archaeological Survey, Recreation, undated (Box-folder 80/1)
  - Along the Old Spanish Trail (From New Mexico to California via Utah), undated (Box-folder 80/2)
  - Mound Builders and Cahokia, undated (Box-folder 80/3)
  - From Nauvoos, Illinois to Utah, undated (Box-folder 80/4)
  - Mesa Verde (slides and 2 audio cassettes), undated (Box-folder 80/5)
  - Some Plains Tribes, Crow, Sioux, Cheyennes, etc., undated (Box-folder 80/6)
  - Plains Indians, Crafts and Arts, undated (Box-folder 80/7)
  - Kutenai, undated (Box-folder 80/8)
  - Pictographs, Montanan, Wyoming, Utah, Nebraska, Kansas, South Dakota, undated (Box-folder 80/9)
  - Plains Indians, Arts and Crafts, undated (Box-folder 80/10)
  - The Nez Perce War, 1877, undated (Box-folder 81/1)
  - Historic Sites Excavations, St. Mary's Jesuit Mission, Montana, undated (Box-folder 81/2)
  - Montana Prehistory, Helena Area, undated (Box-folder 81/3)
  - Montana Pictographs, undated (Box-folder 81/4)
  - Prehistory, North Central and Northeast Montana, undated (Box-folder 81/5)
  - Scenes from Missoula, undated (Box-folder 81/6)
  - North Africa, Berbers, undated (Box-folder 81/7)
  - Egypt, Sinai - Negev, undated (Box-folder 81/8)
  - Grand Canyon National Park, Non-Commercial, undated (Box-folder 81/9)
  - Titles, Cartoons, etc., undated (Box-folder 81/10)
  - Yellowstone, Grand Teton, undated (Box-folder 81/11)
  - Israel, slides and audio cassette, undated (Box-folder 82/1)
  - Greek, Crete, Mycenea, Romans, undated (Box-folder 82/2)
  - Volcano - Mount Lassen, slides and audio cassette, undated (Box-folder 82/3)
  - Custer Battle Field, Smithsonian, undated (Box-folder 82/4)
  - Mesopotamian Archaeology Part I, undated (Box-folder 82/5)
  - Mesopotamian Archaeology Part II, undated (Box-folder 82/6)
  - Archaeology and Religion, undated (Box-folder 82/7)
  - Audio cassettes to accompany Astronomy and Planet Slides, undated (Box-folder 83/1)
  - Galilee Archaeology, undated (Box-folder 83/2)
  - Jerusalen Archaeology, undated (Box-folder 83/3)
  - Lewis and Clark Expedition, include 3s audio cassettes, undated (Box-folder 83/4)
  - America's National Parks and Monuments, undated (Box-folder 83/5)
  - Astronomy and Planets, undated (Box-folder 83/6)
  - New Testament archaeology, undated (Box-folder 83/7)
  - Modern Native Americans, undated (Box-folder 83/8)
  - North American Indians, Florida North to Canada, undated (Box-folder 84/1)
  - North Dakota, Prehistory to History, Tray 1, undated (Box-folder 84/2)
  - North Dakota, Prehistory to History, Tray 2, undated (Box-folder 84/3)
  - Zion National Park, Bryce Canyon National Park, including Some Ancient Pueblo Ruins at Nearby Schonesburg, undated (Box-folder 84/4)
  - The Chaco Phenomenon, Pueblo II Chaco Area, including audio cassette, undated (Box-folder 84/5)
  - Native Americans in the Southwest, Navaho, Apache, and Others, undated (Box-folder 84/6)
  - Northwest Coast Indians, undated (Box-folder 84/7)
  - Anasazi, Pueblo IV, undated (Box-folder 84/8)
  - Anasazi, Basket Maker, Developmental Pueblo (Basket Maker III, Pueblo I, Pueblo II), undated (Box-folder 84/9)
  - Airviews, undated (Box-folder 85/1)
  - Volcano - Mount St. Helens, slides and audio cassette, undated (Box-folder 85/2)
  - Oregon, Washington Scenery, undated (Box-folder 85/3)
  - Ponape, Truk, Bikini Atolls, undated (Box-folder 85/4)
  - Yap, undated (Box-folder 85/5)
  - Utah, undated (Box-folder 85/6)
  - Eskimo, undated (Box-folder 85/7)
  - Western Asia, undated (Box-folder 85/8)
  - Earth Origins, undated (Box-folder 85/9)
  - Europe and Lebanon, undated (Box-folder 85/10)
  - US Cities, Washington DC and New York, undated (Box-folder 85/11)
  - Australia, undated (Box-folder 85/12)
  - Polynesia, undated (Box-folder 86/1)
  - Glacier Park, undated (Box-folder 86/2)
  - Guam, undated (Box-folder 86/3)
  - Guam, Saipan, Marianas, undated (Box-folder 86/4)
  - Pioneer, Fort Laramie, Fort Shaw, undated (Box-folder 86/5)
  - Pictographs, Great Basin, California, Washington, Alaska, undated (Box-folder 86/6)
  - Pipeline, Wyoming, Colorado, undated (Box-folder 86/7)
  - Historic Archaeology (Mines, Ranches, Farms), Helena Area, Canyon Ferry, Fort Benton, undated (Box-folder 86/8)
  - Historic Archaeology, Demersville, Bearmouth, Bannock, Sylvanite Mine, undated (Box-folder 86/9)
  - Buffalo Jumps I, undated (Box-folder 86/10)
  - Colorado and Green River Plateaus, undated (Box-folder 86/11)
  - Mound Builders, undated (Box-folder 86/12)
  - Bannack, Sylvanite Mine, Weeksville, Demersville, undated (Box-folder 87/1)
  - The Chichimeca, U.S. Southwest and Mexico, slides and audio cassette, undated (Box-folder 87/2)
  - Fort Owen, undated (Box-folder 87/3)
  - Historic Sites, Montana, Dakotas, Theodore Roosevelt National Park, Badlands, undated (Box-folder 87/4)
  - Lifeways, Northern Plains Indians II, undated (Box-folder 87/5)
  - Pueblo Native Americans in the Southwest, Hopi, Zuni, Acoma, Lagunza, Taos, undated (Box-folder 87/6)
  - Southwest Pueblo, Santa Clara, undated (Box-folder 87/7)
  - Lifeways, American Indians, undated (Box-folder 87/8)
  - This Land is Yours, Mesopotamia, undated (Box-folder 87/9)
  - Maya Art and Decline, Aztec and Adjoining, undated (Box-folder 87/10)
  - A Few Old Local Railroad Slides Plus Copies of Early Railroad, undated (Box-folder 88/1)
  - Micronesia, undated (Box-folder 88/2)
  - Family, undated (Box-folder 88/3)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box-folder 88/4)
  - Bitterroot Valley, Bitterroot Mountains, undated (Box-folder 88/5)
  - Fillmore, Utah, undated (Boxbox-folder 88/6)